All right!
We're all done, Makabe-kun!
Did you survive somehow, Kojuurou?
Yeah! It's finally summer vacation!
Do you have any plans?
Me? I'm...
Hey, Makabe!
Here it comes!
Super
Exciting
Marine Beach
Okinawa
What in the world are you thinking?
Don't use my desk as your personal trash can.
I'm surprised you figured out it was me.
Anyone would know, considering
you wrote something like this.
Please Contact Your M
Yes... Summer vacation,
when we'll have no classes.
I can't worry about logic when we
won't have classes for forty days.
I'm going to go with the power play.
It's what I learned from Fujinomiya Neko.
Too bad for you...
I already have plans to spend
my summer at our island villa.
Shuri-kun...
You're invited.
What?!
M-Me?
Aren't you excited, Shuri-kun?
She's doing this to spite me.
To spite me personally!
I-I...
I don't wanna go unless Makabe-kun's with me!
Nice, Kojuurou.
That's right, Adagaki-san.
Kojuurou-kyun and I are one and the same.
If you're taking Kojuurou,
you can expect me there, as well.
Wha—
If Masamune-sama is going,
I will also accompany him.
What? That sounds so nice! The beach?
I want to swim until I puke!
I'm so jealous!
Now, what will you do, Adagaki-san?
Will you take care of all of us,
or spend your time on a
private beach all alone?
Those are your choices.
All...
All right, fine!
And so,
we're heading toward an isolated
island called Tsunade Island.
#7 "The Tsunade Island Incident"
Yes!
Time to raise the sails!
Pig's Foot.
Where's the Cruel Princess?
She's still eating.
Putting Aki-sama aside,
I've been researching Fujinomiya Neko.
I can't find a weakness.
I can't figure out why
she's so obsessed with you.
So logically...
There's a boat over there, too.
Well, don't worry, Master.
No matter what happens, my only goal
is to get revenge against Adagaki Aki.
A Fujinomiya Neko or two coming at
me with all she's got is no problem.
This is not the time to sound so carefree.
Wait, is she angry at me?
Pig's Foot...
If you don't do something
about Aki-sama on this trip,
I will tell Aki-sama
everything that's happened thus far.
Wait, what?
What do you mean, I wasn't anything serious?
Are you saying that didn't mean we
were going out? And that's why...
Hey, wait! Hear me out, Kenji! Ken—
Ugh! That selfish bastard!
What is it? What's wrong with me?
That I have a face of a mistress?
That I'm a different woman when drunk?
That I sing death metal at karaoke?!
Yuisaki-san, the young lady has arrived.
Right. I'll be right there.
So gorgeous!
This is what a villa looks like?
To be able to stay somewhere
like this is amazing!
True, it's much fancier than I—
No, no. There's no time to be in awe.
Is she serious about telling her everything?
That's so not fair.
Yuisaki-san should have arrived before us.
Yuisaki-san?
My father's secretary.
Since Yoshino's father was busy,
she came along as a chaperone.
Watching over the young lady of the
house is part of the secretary's job.
My sweet, adorable Aki-sama...
You're the only one who
can comfort me right now.
Open the doors.
You've had a long journey.
We've been waiting for you, Aki-sama.
Wow, she's really pretty!
She looks like an actress!
We'll be in your care, Yuisaki-san.
It's no trouble at all.
I heard that you were
bringing a lot of friends...
And a boy, too?!
M-Milady, what's the meaning of this?
I'm a boy, too.
I will tell Aki-sama everything.
I can't be worried about
appearances any longer.
If I don't make Adagaki
fall for me here, I'll...
W-Well, um...
She's a Cruel Princess who
bears her fangs at men,
Who is that, milady?
but she likes to look good
in front of other women.
Well, um, uh...
This is a super risky move,
but I have to go out on a limb here.
Yes!
I am dating Adagaki-san!
It's a pleasure to meet you.
That hurt!
You're the one saying things
that prove your brain's fried!
So what?! It's not that big a deal!
Yes, it is! It's a huge deal!
Of course...
If you were still going on
about how much you hate men,
I would have been worried.
Y-You think so?
Of course! It's one thing if you're
still in grade school or middle school,
but if you were still saying
you hated men in high school,
if you'll pardon my saying so,
it'd just be embarrassing.
But I'm relieved.
You have such a lovely boyfriend.
Goodness, you should have told me!
R-Right...
This should help with the lack of
development in your breasts, as well.
I... I just thought it wasn't
anything worth mentioning!
Oh, come now. It's hard to find
a boyfriend this handsome.
He's nothing special!
Come on, Makabe!
Huh?
You wanted to go swimming, didn't you?
That brat...
Thank goodness you're so
concerned about appearances.
And whose fault do you think this is?!
You chose this yourself, Adagaki-san.
Even though Adagaki Aki's the Cruel Princess
who gives guys horrible nicknames,
she chooses to maintain appearances
in front of other girls.
That was a really risky wager,
but I read the situation correctly.
Thank goodness the hot secretary
lady wasn't harsh, either.
Well, if you hadn't said something so crazy...
Ah, Yuisaki-san.
Listen well, Makabe. This is just
for while we're on this island.
Huh?
This is just an act,
and you know what'll happen
if you take it too far!
Okay, got it! No problem.
Of course, I'm not going to
let it end as just an act.
Behold! My perfect body
glimmering in the sunlight!
It's the ocean!
Charge!
Huh?
This feels so good!
She's so energetic.
The water's amazing! Come on, everyone!
She might have been a dolphin or
a female diver in her past life.
Makabe-kun, you look as cool as ever.
I'm happy for you, Kojuurou.
You didn't have to wear one of the
swimsuits the class rep picked out.
No!
Of course not! I'm a boy!
Of course I'm going to wear a boy's!
So why are you wearing a T-shirt?
It's so I don't get sunburned.
Isn't it cool? Rawr!
Oh, I see...
You can never be too careful.
UV rays are an enemy to your skin.
Oh, yes, Masamune-sama...
Would you mind going over there
and helping me reapply my sunblock?
E-Eek! A girl's body!
No, wait! If that Yuisaki-san
happens to see this,
the chance I finally earned
from the "we're dating" plan
will go to waste!
Fujinomiya-san, I, um... Uh...
Oh, my.
Why don't you go pull your
cheap tricks somewhere else?
You heard Makabe. He's dating me.
Stop trying to interfere.
Wh-Whoa! To think she'd be
the one to jump on this...
You don't seem nearly as upset
as I'd expect, Aki-sama.
I'm saying this for your sake.
I'm sorry to drag you into this,
but if Yuisaki-san saw this,
she'd get the wrong idea.
Makabe would be the indecisive playboy,
and you'd be the one getting played.
I'm sure that wouldn't look good
for the Fujinomiya family, either.
Very well.
I will withdraw for the time being,
since you're being so calm about this.
I'm glad you comprehend things so quickly.
Huh? Where are we going?
Somewhere quiet. Come with me.
You're my boyfriend, aren't you?
H-Hey, hey... Where is this going?
We're completely alone now.
Makabe...
Bring me some carbs.
It doesn't matter what kind.
What?!
Brr, it's freezing.
Go on, hurry it up.
If you ask Yuisaki-san,
she'll prepare something for you.
U-Um...
What?
Wh-What happened to acting like we're dating?
No one will see us here.
There's not a single micron's worth
of a point to continue this act
where no one can see us.
Are you stupid?
You damn bitch...
Well, if you want to continue, that's fine,
but I still want the same thing.
Hurry and bring me my meal.
Do your best, darling.
Yeah, yeah, I got it.
Please be patient, honey.
If you walk, I'm divorcing you.
Damn it all...
Whether she's in the gym storage room or
at the beach, that sadist never changes.
Anyway, I can't let things go on like this.
I need something that'll push
this one step further.
Um, excuse me.
Oh, Makabe-kun.
I see that Aki-sama hasn't changed.
I'm very sorry about that.
You must be a very kind boyfriend,
to do this for your girlfriend.
No, this much is normal.
Um, may I ask you a question?
Yes?
Are there any fun locations on this island?
Well... There's a club, a live music venue,
and since you're a guy, there's a cabaret club.
Er, I mean something that high-schoolers
on summer break can enjoy.
Oh, I see.
Well...
How about a test of courage?
A test of courage?
Adagaki Aki...
If I recall correctly, she doesn't
handle scary things well.
If I come to save her after her knees
give out and she's unable to move...
I guess that might be too childish.
No, that's great!
Everyone likes those!
Is there a particular place?
Yes. There's a perfect spot.
Thank you.
I won't tell you to blow up, you normie.
You're free to love who you want, after all.
But, but...
It's a hundred years too early
for a little brat like you!
I'm going to send you straight to Hell!
It was the year that I was hired as
the secretary for the Adagaki family.
Yeah, we met at the concert, remember?
Huh? What do you mean you
were just playing around?!
What are you talking about?!
Wait, Midori! You're at work!
Crap, someone's here?
M-Milady? Why are you crying?
Oh, where's that rather round
boy you were playing with?
He's gone!
He's gone already.
I don't need anyone like him!
So she chose pride over being coddled.
What a cute little girl.
Ever since then,
the little lady was supposed to continue
her destructive path of hating men.
Adagaki-san!
Please...
Go out with me!
Nice! Despite her elegant face,
she's a hellish princess who
tramples over the males.
Gives me the chills!
She could probably turn completely dark,
take her negative, man-hating aura,
and conquer the world with it.
And yet...
Where the hell did he come from?
That little pissant with
such a refreshing face?
Well, this definitely has me
trembling with excitement.
Why do you seem so happy?
Did you say something?
I said good for you.
Yeah, really!
Now!
Let's decide what order we're going in.
Who's first?
Second?
I-It's me.
Third?
Me!
Fourth?
And I'm fifth.
It appears that I'm sixth and last.
All right, let's get things rolling. Koiwai-san!
Good luck!
You gave me a great suggestion, Yuisaki-san.
This is the absolutely perfect stage.
I'm next!
Allow me to explain. The starting
order was definitely rigged.
And once the Cruel Princess
is too scared to move,
I will come swooping in to
save her from her distress.
Let's go to the exit together, Adagaki-san.
M-Makabe... You'll forgive me?
Well, I am your boyfriend.
I know it's a bit late, but...
No, not just now... Be my boyfriend forever.
You're so reliable, darling.
Awesome, awesome. Nice!
Huh? It went out?! It won't turn on!
What is this? Why isn't it working?
Are you prepared to be scared
out of your wits, Adagaki Aki?
Is it this way?
You're none of my concern, brat.
I'll go this way.
My only target is Makabe Masamune!
I'm going to turn that hottie mask
of yours into a frightened mess!
Even Aki-sama will be able
to get out of this dungeon.
And you, her boyfriend, will be so
frightened that your knees give out.
There is nothing more embarrassing!
The love between you will disappear!
Nothing will bring me more joy!
Is Aki-sama next? Fear not.
No!
Seriously, what's wrong with this thing?
Here it comes!
Are you all right, Adagaki-san?
Huh?!
Who the hell are you?
Everyone, run!
Yuisaki-san?
No!
This is a dream... This is a dream...
This is a dream... This is a dream!
An incident where everyone gets murdered
on a desert island! A lustful serial killer!
The names of the dead
include Yuisaki Midori!
No! I don't want everyone
to find out how old I am!
Yuisaki-sama? What are you doing here?
Oh, dear...
It appears as though it's going to rain.
N-No!
This is a nightmare!
Oh, are you awake?
You shouldn't move.
You hit your head, so you should stay still.
I'm so sorry, I...
You really startled me.
I asked Koiwai-san to help
me scare people a bit,
but I didn't think you were going
to participate too, Yuisaki-san.
So that's how it is.
But you must be a very
reliable person, Yuisaki-san.
I need to take after you.
That's not true.
You seem to be a boyfriend
who cares for his girlfriend.
That's not true.
Huh?
Actually, it's a lie that
I'm going out with Adagaki-san.
I came up with this test of courage
because I wanted to show off to her.
And I ended up getting you
involved, too, so I'm sorry.
He's a good kid.
And yet I went this far
because I was so prejudiced.
You're late, Makabe!
If you drop Yuisaki-san,
I'll never forgive you!
Milady...
B-But I'll say thank you, at least.
Yuisaki-san, please don't tell
Adagaki-san what I said...
What are you talking about?
Huh?
I didn't hear anything.
I ended up not getting any results.
Pig's Foot.
Yes, I'm sorry!
You don't have to be so on edge.
Huh?
I'm telling you that your plan wasn't so bad.
Aki-sama cares about appearances,
but she refuses to do things
she truly doesn't like.
Doing that in front of Commando
was probably a good thing.
So I won't tell Aki-sama.
I-I see.
Don't let your guard down, Pig's Foot.
I have no intention of helping out
a Pig's Foot who's not motivated.
M-Master!